Franclin James C. Lim

Address: Maraat Matab-ang, Toledo City, Cebu, Philippines

Phone: (+63) 910 202 5612

Email: devfranclinjames@gmail.com

https://www.onlinejobs.ph/jobseekers/info/2992796

https://www.linkedin.com/in/franclinjameslim/

SUMMARY:

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology graduate with 6+ year experienced proven front-end and strong back-end development, Advanced graphics design, and IT:hardware/software/network maintenance. Seeking to leverage skills and experience to contribute into a growing technology era.

Professional Experience:

6 years - 2023: EnfraUSA - Front-end and Back-end Developer, Graphics Designer

- Used OctoberCMS and Salesforce
- Maintain over thousands of websites and provide client-requested designs through the course of my tenure
- Collaborate with professional services team, client support team, migration team, Onboarding team, and FED team
- Front-end Designer for Baystone Media in Dental/Chiropractic/Pediatrics/Veterinary
- Front-end Designer in Officite Dental/Optomentry
- Migration Specialist and Professional cases in Imatrix Websites in Chiropractic/Dental/ Pediatrics/Veterinary/Optometry/Law/Automotive
- October 5, 2017 Present

Freelance: TRUDE LIZARES Clothing - trudelizares.com - Developer/Web Manager

- Used Shopify
- Add new shop items with pricing and details
- Worked on HTML and JQuery scripts and mainly front-end designs
- Used Photoshop and Lightroom edits on photos
- 2020-2023

1 year: IPM-CDC I.T. & GPS Division

- Used HiTechfleetGPS Application
- Managed geofencing and tracking GPS coordinates on company trucks
- IT Network Admin Staff & Database Admin Staff
- Managed Computers, CCTV's, Printers, Network lines
- Installed Operating Systems, Softwares, and GPS Systems
- 2016-2017

Freelance Photography and Videography Services

- Freelance, Events and Wedding Photo Shoot/Video Editing
- Street Video/Photography
- Video Edits under DaVinci/Ae/Pr
- 2013-2023



Educational Background

College - Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, Colegio San Agustin - Bacolod

- Bacolod City, Negros Occidental, Philippines June 2012 - 2016

Highschool - Holy Infant School - Tagbilaran City, Bohol - 2010

Elementary - Mabinay Central School - Mabinay, Negros Oriental - 2006

Skills:

- Advanced knowledge in front-end Design HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, and junior back-end development through PHP, and MySQL
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, JQuery, Twig, React.js, Typescript
- Skilled in Adobe Creative Apps: Photoshop, Illustrator, AfterEffects, PremierePro
- Effective Ability in project management, client communication, and team collaboration
- Strong attention to detail and ability to work under tight deadlines